Guide to the The New Leader Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Photographs, 1906-2005, undated
  - The Transkei, 1974-1976 (Box 189, Folder 161)
  - Travia, Anthony J., 1965 (Box 189, Folder 162)
  - Traxler, Vieri, undated (Box 189, Folder 163)
  - Treen, David C., undated (Box 189, Folder 164)
  - Trieste, 1948, undated (Box 189, Folder 165)
  - Trilling, Diana, undated (Box 189, Folder 166)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1937-1953, undated (Box 189, Folder 167)
  - Troy, William, undated (Box 189, Folder 168)
  - Trudeau, Gen. Arthur, 1962 (Box 189, Folder 169)
  - Trudeau, Pierre Elliot, 1975-1980 (Box 189, Folder 170)
  - Trujillo, Gen., 1954-1959 (Box 189, Folder 171)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1950, 1953, undated (Box 189, Folder 172)
  - Truman, Margaret, 1952 (Box 189, Folder 173)
  - Truman plot, 1950 (Box 189, Folder 174)
  - Semyon, Tsarapkin, 1961-1962 (Box 189, Folder 175)
  - Tshombe, Moise, undated (Box 189, Folder 176)
  - Tsiang, T.F., undated (Box 189, Folder 177)
  - Tubman, William V.S., 1947, 1954 (Box 189, Folder 178)
  - Tunisia, 1940-1976, undated (Box 189, Folder 179)
  - Turkey--Scenes, 1931-1967, undated (Box 189, Folder 180)
  - Tunku Abdul Rahman, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 181)
  - Turner, Stansfield, 1977, 1979, undated (Box 189, Folder 182)
  - TVA, undated (Box 189, Folder 183)
  - Twining, Gen. Nathan F., 1950-1959 (Box 189, Folder 184)
  - Tydings, Millard, 1950 (Box 189, Folder 185)
  - Tyndall, John, 1977 (Box 189, Folder 186)
  - Tyrol, undated (Box 189, Folder 187)
  - Udall, Morris, 1975-1976 (Box 189, Folder 188)
  - Udall, Stewart, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 189)
  - Ulbricht, Walter, 1957-1961 (Box 189, Folder 190)
  - Umberto, King, undated (Box 189, Folder 191)
  - Unemployment, 1957-1975, undated (Box 189, Folder 192)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 189, Folder 193)
  - United Nations
    - Human Rights, 1952-1986 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - WHO, 1942-1999 (Personalities, Meetings, etc.) (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Meetings and Buildings, 1951-1998, undated (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Peacekeeping, 1964-2000, undated (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - United States
    - Aid Overseas, 1951-1962, undated (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Communists in Action, 1941-1949 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Capitol, 1954-1965 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Congress, 1961-1981 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Constitution, undated (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Economy--Scenes-- Including Unemployment and Supermarkets, 1949-1971, undated (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Environment Problems, 1953-1971, undated (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Flag, undated (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Health, undated (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Industry--Scenes, 1946-1967, undated (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Justice, 1946-1972 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Military, 1957-1981, undated (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Poverty, 1937-1969, undated (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Scenes, 1936-1983, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 190, Folder 18 to 19)
    - Space Program, 1958-1971, undated (See also Missiles) (Box 190, Folder 20)
    - State Department, 1960-1976, undated (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - Underworlds--Gangsters, 1929-1963, undated (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - Students, 1955-1971, undated (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - White House, 1952-1970, undated (Box 190, Folder 24)
  - U Nu, undated (Box 190, Folder 25)
  - Urquhart, Brian, 1982-1984 (Box 190, Folder 26)
  - Uruguay, 1960-1965 (Box 190, Folder 27)
  - Uspensky, Igor and Inna, undated (Box 190, Folder 28)
  - Ustinov, Dimitry, 1971-1980 (Box 190, Folder 29)
  - Vajpayee, Atal, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 30)
  - Valtin, Jan, 1943, undated (Box 190, Folder 31)
  - Vance, Cyrus, 1976-1978, undated (Box 190, Folder 32)
  - Vandenberg, Arthur, 1948-1950 (Box 190, Folder 33)
  - Vandenberg, Hoyt S., undated (Box 190, Folder 34)
  - Van Den Dreshd, undated (Box 190, Folder 35)
  - Van Doren, Charles, 1959 (Box 190, Folder 36)
  - Van Fleet, James A., 1951-1953, undated (Box 190, Folder 37)
  - Vang Pao, 1969-1970 (Box 190, Folder 38)
  - Van Mook, H.J., undated (Box 190, Folder 39)
  - Vaan, John Paul, 1970 (Box 190, Folder 40)
  - Van Ty, Gen. Le, 1955, 1960 (Vietnam) (Box 190, Folder 41)
  - Vargas, Getulio, 1945, 1950 (Box 190, Folder 42)
  - Vatican--Scenes, 1963, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 43)
  - Vaughn, Jack, 1969, 1970 (Box 190, Folder 44)
  - Velasco, Juan, 1969 (Box 190, Folder 45)
  - Velde, Harold, 1954, undated (Box 190, Folder 46)
  - Venezuela, 1951-1964, undated (Box 190, Folder 47)
  - Venizelos, Sophocles, 1949 (Box 190, Folder 48)
  - Versailles Treaty, undated (Box 190, Folder 49)
  - Verwoerd, Hendrick Frensch, 1958-1966 (Box 190, Folder 50)
  - Victoria, Queen, undated (Box 190, Folder 51)
  - Videla, Gen. Jorge, undated (Argentina) (Box 190, Folder 52)
  - Nguyen Lun Vien, undated (Box 190, Folder 53)
  - Vienna--Scenes, 1946-1955, undated (Box 190, Folder 54)
  - Vienna Summit--Salt Treaty, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 55)
  - Vienna Youth Festival, 1959 (Box 190, Folder 56)
  - Vietnam
    - Buddhists, 1963 (Box 190, Folder 57)
    - Conferences--Honolulu and Guam, 1965-1967 (Box 190, Folder 58)
    - Coup, 1960-1964 (Box 190, Folder 59)
    - Demonstrations, 1965-1985 (Box 190, Folder 60)
    - Leaders--North, 1969, undated (Box 190, Folder 61)
    - Newsman/Reporters, undated (Box 190, Folder 62)
    - Paris Peace Talks, 1968 (Box 190, Folder 63)
    - Refugees, 1974, 1978, undated (Box 190, Folder 64)
    - Scenes, 1965-1975, undated (Box 190, Folder 65)
  - Vietnam War, 1947-1975, undated (Box 190, Folder 66 to 67)
  - Vincent, John Carter, undated (Box 190, Folder 68)
  - Vinson, Carl, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 69)
  - Vinson, Fred M., 1946, undated (Box 190, Folder 70)
  - Vishinsky, Audrei, undated (Box 190, Folder 71)
  - Vittorio Di, undated (Box 190, Folder 72)
  - Vivas, Rafael and Gilberto, undated (Box 190, Folder 73)
  - Voice of America, undated (Box 190, Folder 74)
  - Volcker, Paul, 1982-1987 (Box 190, Folder 75)
  - Von Bonin, undated (Box 190, Folder 76)
  - Von Braun, Wernher, 1958, undated (Box 190, Folder 77)
  - Von Brentano, Heinrich, undated (Box 190, Folder 78)
  - Von Hassel, Rai-Uwe, 1964,1966 (Box 190, Folder 79)
  - Von Thadded, Adolf, 1962, 1969 (Box 190, Folder 80)
  - Vorontsov, Yuliy M., 1991 (Box 190, Folder 81)
  - Voroshilov, Marhsall Klemcuti, 1953, undated (Box 190, Folder 82)
  - Vorys, John M., 1950 (Box 190, Folder 83)
  - Vorster, Balthazar Johannes, 1962-1975 (Box 190, Folder 84)
  - Voting Scenes, 1944-1960, undated (Box 190, Folder 85)
  - Vukmanovic, Svetozar, 1957 (Box 190, Folder 86)
  - Wagner, Robert F., 1953, 1960, undated (Box 190, Folder 87)
  - Walcott, Jesse, 1948 (Box 190, Folder 88)
  - Waldheim, Kurt, 1972-1979 (Box 190, Folder 89)
  - Walesa, Lech, 1980, 1989, undated (Box 190, Folder 90)
  - Walker, Daniel, undated (Box 190, Folder 91)
  - Walker, Gen. Edwin A., 1961-1962 (Box 190, Folder 92)
  - Walker, Richard L., undated (Box 190, Folder 93)
  - Wall Street, 1929-1981, undated (Box 190, Folder 94)
  - Wallace, George, 1963-1972 (Governor of Alabama) (Box 190, Folder 95)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1949-1953, undated (Box 190, Folder 96)
  - Wallace, Lurleen, 1964-1966 (Box 190, Folder 97)
  - Walter, Francis, undated (Box 190, Folder 98)
  - Walters, Vernon, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 99)
  - Wang Hung-Wen, 1973 (Box 190, Folder 100)
  - Ward, Dr. Harry, 1930 (Box 190, Folder 101)
  - Waring, Judge J. Waites, undated (Box 190, Folder 102)
  - Warner, John, 1972-1979 (Box 190, Folder 103)
  - Warnke, Paul C., 1977-1978, undated (Box 190, Folder 104)
  - Warren, Earl, 1957-1965, undated (Box 190, Folder 105)
  - Warsaw Pact Maneuvers--Polish Border, 1981 (Box 190, Folder 106)
  - Washington, D.C., 1955-1973 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Washington, Walter, 1968-1969 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Watergate, 1969 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Watkins, Arthur V., 1949-1954, undated (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Watson, James, undated (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Wazzan, Shafik, 1981 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Weaver, Robert C., 1960-1966 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Webb, James, 1949 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Weaponry, 1959-1970 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Webb, Sidney and Beatrice, undated (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Wechsler, James A., 1953 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Webster, Martin, 1978 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - Weddington, Sarah, 1978 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Wedemeyer, Gen. Albert, undated (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - Weeda, Robert, 1993 (Box 191, Folder 15)
  - Weeks, Sinclair, 1952, undated (Box 191, Folder 16)
  - Wehbe, Mikhail, 2003 (Box 191, Folder 17)
  - Wehner, Herbert, 1964-1973 (Box 191, Folder 18)
  - Weil, Simone, 1974-1979 (Box 191, Folder 19)
  - Weinberger, Caspar, 1981-1983 (Box 191, Folder 20)
  - Weiss, Ted, 1986 (Box 191, Folder 21)
  - Weizman, Chaim, 1948, undated (Box 191, Folder 22)
  - Weizman, Ezer, 1978, undated (Box 191, Folder 23)
  - Welch, Robert, 1961 (Box 191, Folder 24)
  - Welensky, Ro, 1960-1961 (Rhodesia-Nyasaland) (Box 191, Folder 25)
  - Welfare, 1967-1977 (Box 191, Folder 26)
  - West Berlin, 1945-1959, undated (Box 191, Folder 27)
  - West Point, 1944-1976 (Box 191, Folder 28)
  - West Virginia--Scenes, 1951-1964 (Box 191, Folder 29)
  - Westmoreland, Gen. William, 1960-1967 (Box 191, Folder 30)
  - Wetbacks, 1948-1959 (Box 191, Folder 31)
  - Wheat, 1947-1950, undated (Box 191, Folder 32)
  - Wheeler, Gen., 1964-1967 (Box 191, Folder 33)
  - Wheelock, Jaime, 1984 (Box 191, Folder 34)
  - Wherry, Kenneth S., undated (Box 191, Folder 35)
  - White, Byron, 1972 (Box 191, Folder 36)
  - White, Harry Dexter, undated (Box 191, Folder 37)
  - White, Gen. Thomas D., 1948-1962 (Box 191, Folder 38)
  - White, John C., 1977-1978 (Box 191, Folder 39)
  - White, Walter, undated (Box 191, Folder 40)
  - Whitelaw, William, undated (Box 191, Folder 41)
  - Whiteside, Thurmon, undated (Box 191, Folder 42)
  - Whitlam, E. Gough, 1969-1974 (Box 191, Folder 43)
  - Wiesner, Jerome, 1961-1969 (Box 191, Folder 44)
  - Wild West, 1869-1889, undated (Box 191, Folder 45)
  - Wiley, Alexander, 1947-1948, undated (Box 191, Folder 46)
  - Wilhelm, Kaiser, undated (Box 191, Folder 47)
  - Williams, G. Mennen, 1952-1960, undated (Box 191, Folder 48)
  - Wilkins, Roy, 1955-1963, undated (Box 191, Folder 49)
  - Williams, Jr., Sen. Harrison A., 1974-1977 (Box 191, Folder 50)
  - Williams, John Bell, 1967-1969, undated (Box 191, Folder 51)
  - Williams, Mrs. Lucille Pickett, 1967 (Box 191, Folder 52)
  - Williams, Shirley, 1975-1977 (Box 191, Folder 53)
  - Wilson, Charles E., 1950-1952, undated (Box 191, Folder 54)
  - Wilson, Harold, 1960-1974 (Box 191, Folder 55)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, undated (Box 191, Folder 56)
  - Winkler, Dr. Pavel, undated (Box 191, Folder 57)
  - Winter Scenes, 1947-1958, undated (Box 191, Folder 58)
  - Winterton, undated (Box 191, Folder 59)
  - Wirtz, Willard, 1963, undated (Box 191, Folder 60)
  - Witt, Nathan, undated (Box 191, Folder 61)
  - Wittfogel, Karl A., 1951 (Box 191, Folder 62)
  - Wolfe, Bertram, undated (Box 191, Folder 63)
  - Wolfe, Thomas, undated (Box 191, Folder 64)
  - Wollweber, Ernst, 1953 (Box 191, Folder 65)
  - Wood, John S., undated (Box 191, Folder 66)
  - Woodcock, Leonard, 1970-1975 (Box 191, Folder 67)
  - Woods, Tighe, undated (Box 191, Folder 68)
  - Woolton, Lord, undated (Box 191, Folder 69)
  - Workers, 1947, undated (Box 191, Folder 70)
  - Workmen's Circle, 1952-1975, undated (Box 191, Folder 71)
  - World Bank, 1971-1979 (Box 191, Folder 72)
  - World Health Organization, 1980, undated (Box 191, Folder 73)
  - Woytinsky, W.S., undated (Box 191, Folder 74)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd, undated (Box 191, Folder 75)
  - Wriston, Walter, 1980, 1984 (Box 191, Folder 76)
  - Wu, K.C., undated (Box 191, Folder 77)
  - Wu Xueqian, 1983 (Box 191, Folder 78)
  - Wujec, Henryk, undated (Box 191, Folder 79)
  - Wyszynski, Cardinal, 1956-1976 (Box 191, Folder 80)
  - Yacobi, Gad, 1992 (Box 191, Folder 81)
  - Yadin, Yigael, 1973, 1977 (Box 191, Folder 82)
  - Yahya Khan, 1970-1971 (Box 191, Folder 83)
  - Yalta Conference, undated (Box 191, Folder 84)
  - Yomani, Sheik Ahmed Zaki, 1976 (Box 191, Folder 85)
  - Yamashita, Gen. Tomoyuki, 1945 (Box 191, Folder 86)
  - Yarborough, Ralph, 1956 (Box 191, Folder 87)
  - Yeltsin, Boris, 1995 (Box 191, Folder 88)
  - Yemen, 1957-1963, undated (Box 191, Folder 89)
  - York, E.T., undated (Box 191, Folder 90)
  - Yorty, Sam, 1954-1969, undated (Box 191, Folder 91)
  - Yosef, Ouadia, undated (Box 191, Folder 92)
  - Yoshida, Shigeru, undated (Box 191, Folder 93)
  - Yost, Charles, 1969 (Box 191, Folder 94)
  - Young, Milton, 1949-1956, undated (Box 191, Folder 95)
  - Young, Dr. Norman, undated (Box 191, Folder 96)
  - Yuasa, Hachiro, undated (Box 191, Folder 97)
  - Youth Festivals--Red, 1962, undated (Box 191, Folder 98)
  - Young, Andrew, 1974-1979 (Box 191, Folder 99)
  - Yugoslavia--Scenes, 1934-2000, undated (Box 191, Folder 100)
  - Zaccaghini, Benigno, 1978-1979, undated (Box 191, Folder 101)
  - Zahedi, undated (Box 191, Folder 102)
  - Zaire, 1978 (Box 191, Folder 103)
  - Zambia, 1961-1965 (Box 191, Folder 104)
  - Zanzibar, 1963 (Box 191, Folder 105)
  - Zapotocky, undated (Box 191, Folder 106)
  - Zarb, Frank, 1974-1975 (Box 191, Folder 107)
  - Zhao, Ziyang, 1984 (Box 191, Folder 108)
  - Zhivkov, Todor, 1957-1986 (Box 191, Folder 109)
  - Zhou, Enlar, 1961 (Box 191, Folder 110)
  - Zhukov, Grigori, 1945, undated (Box 191, Folder 111)
  - Zia ul-Haq, Gen. Mohammed, 1980-1981, undated (Box 191, Folder 112)
  - Zimbabwe, 1935, undated (Box 191, Folder 113)
  - Zimmerman, Warren, 1986 (Box 191, Folder 114)
  - Zoli, Adore, undated (Box 191, Folder 115)
  - Zorin, Valerian, 1960-1962 (Box 191, Folder 116)
  - Zwicker, Gen. Ralph, 1954 (Box 191, Folder 117)
  - Subseries 2: Photographs from Correspondence, 1941-1954, undated
    Subseries 2 includes photographs removed from the Correspondence in Series II and the Subject Files in Series III. Copies of the photographs remain in the original location, and the photographs are sorted alphabetically by the folder title of the original location.
    - Alexander, Robert J., undated (Box 191, Folder 118-119)
    - Angell, Norman, undated (Box 191, Folder 120)
    - Atkinson, Oriana, 1948 (Box 191, Folder 121)
    - Bernays, Edward, 1947-1953 (Box 191, Folder 122)
    - Brown, Irving, 1947-1953 (Box 191, Folder 123)
    - Bun-Bur, 1950-1953 (Box 191, Folder 124)
    - Cha-Chi, 1948-1953 (Box 191, Folder 125)
    - F--General, 1944-1952 (Box 191, Folder 126)
    - Fischer, Alfred Joachim, 1949-1953 (Box 191, Folder 127)
    - Fitch, Geraldine, 1948 (Mrs. George Fitch) (Box 191, Folder 128)
    - G--General, 1942-1951 (Box 191, Folder 129)
    - Gre-Hah, 1939-1959 (Box 191, Folder 130)
    - Hamori, 1953-1959 (Box 191, Folder 131)
    - Hellin, Frederick, 1947-1952d (Box 191, Folder 132)
    - Henderson, Leon, 1946-1951 (Box 191, Folder 133)
    - Hicks, Granville, undated (Box 191, Folder 134)
    - Naoi, Takeo, undated (Box 191, Folder 135)
    - Olberg, Paul, undated (Box 191, Folder 136)
    - Oliver, Robert T., undated (Box 191, Folder 137)
    - Polubotuo, Aglaya--Polish American Congress, undated (Box 191, Folder 138)
    - Pusta, Kaarel R., Sr., undated (Box 191, Folder 139)
    - Putnam, Samuel, undated (Box 191, Folder 140)
    - R--General, undated (Box 191, Folder 141)
    - Seed, William H., undated (Box 191, Folder 142)
    - Shafer, William A., undated (Box 191, Folder 143)
    - Sol, undated (Box 191, Folder 144)
    - Viereck, Peter, undated (Box 191, Folder 145)
    - Wofford, Harris L., Jr., undated (Box 191, Folder 146)
    - Anniversary Dinner, undated (Box 191, Folder 147)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity Photographs, 1906-2004, undated
    Subseries 3 includes stock publicity photographs of writers, dancers, musicians, and actors, which are sorted alphabetically by subject.
    - Art
      - A-C, 1906-1993, undated (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - D-F, 1946-1998, undated (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - G-J, 1960-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - K-M, 1964-1998, undated (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - N-Q, 1951-1999, undated (Box 192, Folder 5)
      - R-T, 1984-1996, undated (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - U-Z, 1935-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 7)
      - General 1960-1993, undated (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Authors
      - A, 1976-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 9)
      - B, 1926-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 10)
      - C, 1936-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 11)
      - D 1943-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 12)
      - E, 1860-2001, undated (Box 192, Folder 13)
      - F, 1925-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 14)
      - G, 1929-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 15)
      - H, 1929-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 16)
      - I-J, 1904-1998, undated (Box 192, Folder 17)
      - K, 1965-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 18)
      - L, 1957-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 19)
      - M, 1944-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 20)
      - N-O, 1969-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 21)
      - P-Q, 1849-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 22)
      - R, 1971-2002, undated (Box 192, Folder 23)
      - S, 1937-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 24)
      - T, 1942-2003, undated (Box 192, Folder 25)
      - U-V, 1949-2001, undated (Box 192, Folder 26)
      - Authors W, 1947-2003, undated (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - Authors Y-Z, 1962-2003, undated (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Dance
      - A-B, 1975-1997, undated (Box 193, Folder 3)
      - C-D, 1970-1996, undated (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - E-F, 1990-1992, undated (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - G-H, 1990-1991, undated (Box 193, Folder 6)
      - I-J, 1987-1997, undated (Box 193, Folder 7)
      - K-L, 1991-1992, undated (Box 193, Folder 8)
      - M-N, 1986-1992, undated (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - O-Q, 1925, 1992, undated (Box 193, Folder 10)
      - R-S, 1988-1998, undated (Box 193, Folder 11)
      - Scenes, 1984-1990, undated (Box 193, Folder 12)
      - T-W, 1986-1997, undated (Box 193, Folder 13)
      - X-Z, 1990 (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Media
      - A, 1986-2002 (Box 193, Folder 15)
      - B, 1989-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 16)
      - C, 1979-2003 (Box 193, Folder 17)
      - D, 1982-2002 (Box 193, Folder 18)
      - E, 1982-2001, undated (Box 193, Folder 19)
      - F, 1989, 2004 (Box 193, Folder 20)
      - G, 1989-2003, undated (Box 193, Folder 21)
      - H, 1992-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 22)
      - I-K, 1989-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 23)
      - L, 1955-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 24)
      - M, 1954-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 25)
      - N, 1989-1996 (Box 193, Folder 26)
      - P-Q, 1937-2003, undated (Box 193, Folder 27)
      - O, 1865-2003, undated (Box 193, Folder 28)
      - R, 1987-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 29)
      - S, 1971-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 30)
      - T, 1991-2003 (Box 193, Folder 31)
      - U-W, 1990-2004 (Box 193, Folder 32)
      - X-Z, 1992-2003 (Box 193, Folder 33)
    - Music
      - General--Instruments and People, 1990, undated (Box 193, Folder 34)
      - A-C, 1938-2001, undated (Box 193, Folder 35)
      - D-F, 1954-1998, undated (Box 193, Folder 36)
      - G-I, 1934-1998, undated (Box 193, Folder 37)
      - J-L, 1935-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 38)
      - M-O, 1974-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 39)
      - P-R, 1918-2000, undated (Box 193, Folder 40)
      - S-U, 1978-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 41)
      - V-Z, 1956-2000, undated (Box 193, Folder 42)
    - Stage and Screen
      - General--People and Scenes, 1903-1975 (Box 193, Folder 43)
      - A-B, 1931-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 44)
      - C-D, 1982-1998, undated (Box 193, Folder 45)
      - E-F, 1989-2000 (Box 193, Folder 46)
      - G-I, 1931-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 47)
      - J-K, 1979-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 48)
      - L-M, 1929-2004, undated (Box 193, Folder 49)
      - N-P, 1936-2001, undated (Box 193, Folder 50)
      - Q-R, 1947-1998, undated (Box 193, Folder 51)
      - S-T, 1985-2003, undated (Box 193, Folder 52)
      - U-W, 1984-2002, undated (Box 193, Folder 53)
      - X-Z, 1996-1998, undated (Box 193, Folder 54)
  - Subseries 4: Oversized Photographs, 1937-1954, undated
    Subseries 4 includes oversized photographs found throughout The New Leader records. They are sorted alphabetically by subject, when known.
    - 50th Testimonial Birthday Dinner for Samuel Levitas, May 14, 1944, (2 Folders) (Box 194, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Jewish Daily Forward Board of Directors, 1939 (framed) (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - The New Leader Anniversary Dinners
      - 14th Anniversary Dinner, 1937 April, (2 Folders) (Box 194, Folder 4 to 5)
      - 15th Anniversary Dinner, 1938 April (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - 30th Anniversary Dinner, 1954 October (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - New York World Telegram--Paris Headlines, 1940-1944 (framed) (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Photo, undated (framed) (Box 172, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Scrapbooks, 1941-1980, undated
  This series contains scrapbooks filled with advertising and promotional materials, as well as clippings of stories that mention The New Leader, and American Labor Conference newsletters and other materials. The series is arranged alphabetically, by each scrapbook’s title, and then chronologically.
  - American Labor Conference--Appeals, 1941-1946 (Box 195)
  - American Labor Conference--Newsletters, 1943-1945 (Box 196)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1962 (Box 197)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1976 (Box 198)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1951-1954 (Box 199)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1955-1958 (Box 200)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1958-1960 (Box 201)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1965 (Box 202)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1980 (Box 203)
  - Promotional Materials, pre-1960 (Box 204)
  - Promotional Materials, 1959-1968 (Box 205)
- Series VIII: Ephemera, 1918-1989, undated
  This series holds an American flag that had once flown above the U.S. Capitol. It has The New Leader’s laminated 1924 certificate of incorporation, as well as seals for stamping important documents and audio recordings of speeches given during a New Leader anniversary event.
  - Audio Recordings
    - Mondale--The New Leader Dinner, 1973 (2 cassettes and 1 magnetic recording tape) (Box 206)
    - Navasky-Newfield Interview, undated (1 cassette) (Box 206)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1924 (Box 207)
  - Election Pin--Tyler, undated (Box 207)
  - Flag--United States, 1989 (Box 207)
  - Seals--New York Call and American Federation of Labor, 1918-1945 (Box 208)